Spare him
Помиловать его
All the court officials are waiting for a result
Все чиновники ждут результата
Who will take the blame for treason?
кто понесёт наказание за мятеж
You?
Ты
Or your elder brother?
Или твой старший брат
Or will you investigate further
Или ты хочешь копать дальше
And break with the Chen family?
и рвать отношения с кланом Чэнь
Do you think
Ты думаешь
Only you can see the situation clearly?
только ты можешь видеть реальное положение дел
Can't I see it clearly?
Я что хуже тебя
Father
Благодарю отецгосударь
Our Sikong family
Наш род Сыкун
After the great chaos
пережил великую смуту
Could still establish itself in the south
и смог закрепиться на юге
Relied on two great families
опираясь на две великие семьи
The Zu family leading troops abroad
Семья Цзу командует армией
The Chen family governing court affairs
семья Чэнь управляет двором
These two families
Эти две семьи
If either corner collapses
если одна из них рухнет
The entire structure will fall
рухнет всё здание
Now
Сейчас
We're not yet firmly established
мы ещё не укрепились
It's not yet time to move against them
не время трогать их
So
Поэтому
The troops were
войска
Deployed by Chu Huan
привёл Чу Хуань
The weapons and armor
оружие и доспехи
Were also planted by Chu Huan to frame you
тоже его подстава
This is
Это
The only way to save you
единственный способ тебя спасти
Do you understand?
Ты понял
I've told you so much
Я столько тебе сказал
Answer
Отвечай